[Music] We have been
hearing this since childhood Who has seen tomorrow
Today I am feeling it for the first time
Who would have thought that we would have to think twice before leaving the house Forget
hugging, even shaking hands will be
difficult
Now no one will say God bless on sneezing
Guests will be welcomed
with sanitizer Knowledge and
science will surprise you The
faces of superheroes will change Who would have thought that Grandparents will turn out to be
rockstars on the Baa
Internet and dude folk will
learn cooking We will care so much for our loved ones We will
value our life so much
That we will look at tomorrow not tomorrow From today
When something is priceless, we don't take any chances
[Music] That is why
ICICI Prudential Life
's iProtect Smart All in One Term
Plan We will look at tomorrow today